export const WHAT_IS_HOSTING = [
    {
        questionNumber: 1,
        question: "I am document which can be displayed in a web browser such as Firefox, Google Chrome, Opera, Microsoft Edge, or Apple Safari. These are also often called just 'pages'. What am I?",
        options: [
            "A web server",
            "A website",
            "A search engine",
            "A web page"
        ],
        answer:
            "A web page",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 2,
        question: "I am a collection of web pages which are grouped together and usually connected together in various ways. Often called a 'site'. What am I?",
        options: [
            "A web server",
            "A website",
            "A search engine",
            "A web page"
        ],
        answer:
            "A website",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 3,
        question: "I am a computer that hosts a website on the Internet. What am I?",
        options: [
            "A web server",
            "A website",
            "A search engine",
            "A web page"
        ],
        answer:
            "A web server",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 4,
        question: "I am a web service that helps you find other web pages, such as Google, Bing, Yahoo, or DuckDuckGo. I'm normally accessed through a web browser. What am I?",
        options: [
            "A web server",
            "A website",
            "A search engine",
            "A web page"
        ],
        answer:
            "A search engine",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 5,
        question: "Hosting is the _____ of your website.",
        options: [
            "Function",
            "Home",
            "Address",
        ],
        answer:
            "Home",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 6,
        question: "If you want a website, you need a host. 'Shared hosting' is an option. This is when...",
        options: [
            "Many websites have their own physical server in one physical data centre.",
            "Many websites share one physical server that hosts all of their websites.",
            "Many websites share one physical server, but each have their own virtual server that hosts their website.",
        ],
        answer:
            "Many websites share one physical server that hosts all of their websites.",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 7,
        question: "Another option is 'Virtual Private Server' hosting. This is when...",
        options: [
            "Many websites have their own physical server in one physical data centre.",
            "Many websites share one physical server that hosts all of their websites.",
            "Many websites share one physical server, but each have their own virtual server that hosts their website.",
        ],
        answer:
            "Many websites share one physical server, but each have their own virtual server that hosts their website.",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 8,
        question: "Another option is 'Dedicated Server' hosting. This is when...",
        options: [
            "Many websites have their own physical server in one physical data centre.",
            "Many websites share one physical server that hosts all of their websites.",
            "Many websites share one physical server, but each have their own virtual server that hosts their website.",
        ],
        answer:
            "Many websites have their own physical server in one physical data centre.",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 9,
        question: "When you order a hosting service, what you're actually paying for is the...",
        options: [
            "Rent for the server's location within it's data centre.",
            "Bragging rights.",
            "Physical disk space on the server, as well as the bandwidth (which is the network connection).",
        ],
        answer:
            "Physical disk space on the server, as well as the bandwidth (which is the network connection).",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 10,
        question: "In order to manage the hosting of your website you'll need access to a friendly UI called a...",
        options: [
            "Control Panel",
            "Cluster Role",
            "Virtual Dashoboard",
        ],
        answer:
            "Control Panel",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 11,
        question: "An issue with 'Shared hosting' is that another website on the same server could reduce your websites bandwidth. True or false?",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        answer:
            "True",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 12,
        question: "This bandwidth issue (and potential DDOS issue) is also a problem with 'Virtual Private Servers'. True or false?",
        options: [
            "True. All your folders are still on the same operating system as all the other websites.",
            "False. While still on the same physical server as other websites, your server is treated as it's own separate computer with it's own operating system, so you are guarenteed the resources you're paying for."
        ],
        answer:
            "False. While still on the same physical server as other websites, your server is treated as it's own separate computer with it's own operating system, so you are guarenteed the resources you're paying for.",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
];